<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to Express Media on Express Media</title><link>https://expressmedia.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to Express Media on Express Media</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://expressmedia.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>政策分析 - 陳時中說要讓台北市的公共廁所裝免治馬桶 - 這樣就可以讓台北變乾淨嗎？</title><link>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/chen/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/chen/</guid><description>&lt;p>民進黨台北市長候選人陳時中9/3日與網路評論員四叉貓拍攝宣傳片，說要讓台北市內一共3763間公共廁所裝免治馬桶，讓國內外觀光客有舒服的體驗。陳時中還因為宣傳片的正當性惹上不少風波。先不論宣傳片的內容是否正當，我們先來看看這個政策本身有什麼問題。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Basic HTML Elements</title><link>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/basic-elements/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/basic-elements/</guid><description>&lt;p>The main purpose of this article is to make sure that all basic HTML Elements are decorated with CSS so as to not miss any possible elements when creating new themes for Hugo.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Creating a New Theme</title><link>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid><description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description></item><item><title>About Hugo</title><link>https://expressmedia.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://expressmedia.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim Have questions or suggestions?</description></item><item><title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title><link>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/goisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/goisforlovers/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo uses the excellent &lt;a href="https://golang.org/">Go&lt;/a> &lt;a href="https://golang.org/pkg/html/template/">html/template&lt;/a> library for
its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very
small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of
logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other
template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of
similarities in Go templates.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Hugo</title><link>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/hugoisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid><description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313 Corresponding pseudo commands:</description></item><item><title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title><link>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://expressmedia.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid><description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description></item></channel></rss>